<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home Design on Bedroom Furniture Ideas</title>
    <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/categories/home-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home Design on Bedroom Furniture Ideas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright 2022 [homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture](https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/categories/home-design/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>11 Sample Shared Bedroom Ideas For Mom And Toddler With New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/shared-bedroom-ideas-for-mom-and-toddler/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/shared-bedroom-ideas-for-mom-and-toddler/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Sample Shared Bedroom Ideas For Mom And Toddler With New Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, To help you get started, we’ve combed the web to find some major inspiration for your shared space. A wall easel will keep your little one’s artwork in a confined space without getting scattered all over the room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/www.mothermag.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/Via-Mini-Piccolini.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sharing Bedroom With Baby Decor Ideas and Inspiration&#34; title=&#34;Sharing Bedroom With Baby Decor Ideas and Inspiration&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Sharing Bedroom With Baby Decor Ideas and Inspiration From mothermag.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the toughest things about having your children share a room is that all privacy disappears. Our first three sons, born within 3 1/2 years of each other, have always shared a room. One fun kids bedroom idea is to incorporate bunk beds with curtains! Make up a special bed in your room (using your child’s mattress), let him decide where to put it in the room, and thank him for helping to teach baby how to be a good sleeper.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Oak Shelves With Brackets With New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/oak-shelves-with-brackets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/oak-shelves-with-brackets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Oak Shelves With Brackets With New Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Here we have a selection oak wall shelf brackets made from solid oak as well as a range of solid oak corbels for shelf. With a colour choice of natural oak, dark oak and tudor oak our chunky oak shelf comes with metal brackets made from raw steel that are handcrafted locally by our highly experienced craftsmen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/img1.etsystatic.com/035/0/5538606/il_fullxfull.597150581_3wnn.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wood Wall Shelf 24 Oak Bracket Wall Shelf 8 Deep&#34; title=&#34;Wood Wall Shelf 24 Oak Bracket Wall Shelf 8 Deep&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Wood Wall Shelf 24 Oak Bracket Wall Shelf 8 Deep From etsy.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted some shelves for my office. We finish the brackets in the same premium wood stain colour chosen for your shelf, seamlessly matching them. With a colour choice of natural oak, dark oak and tudor oak our chunky oak shelf comes with metal brackets made from raw steel that are handcrafted locally by our highly experienced craftsmen. Textured / weathered / distressed rustic oak floating shelf.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Urban Teenage Bedroom Ideas With New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/urban-teenage-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/urban-teenage-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Urban Teenage Bedroom Ideas With New Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Vintage teenage girl bedroom ideas; A bedroom design with a variety of decor elements will create a space that&#39;s as unique as your.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i0.wp.com/www.dwellingdecor.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/Trendy-Teen-Bedroom-Ideas-Dwellingdecor.png?w=1041&amp;amp;amp;ssl=1&#34; alt=&#34;21 Best Teen’s Bedroom Design Ideas&#34; title=&#34;21 Best Teen’s Bedroom Design Ideas&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
21 Best Teen’s Bedroom Design Ideas From dwellingdecor.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most important thing about your son or daughter&#39;s bedroom makeover is making it something that you embark on together. Your teen&#39;s bedroom should be just as creative and artistic as they are. Urban grey teenage girl bedroom ideas; A teen girl’s room is where she gets her homework done, entertains friends, discovers new hobbies, dreams about the future, and matures from a tween into a young woman.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 Sample Small Swimming Pools With DIY</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/small-swimming-pools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/small-swimming-pools/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Sample Small Swimming Pools With DIY&lt;/strong&gt;, We’ve been selling pools online for over 20 years and we’ve got the expertise to help answer all of your questions. Compact size inground pool with slide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i1.wp.com/magzhouse.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/Awesome-Small-Pools-Design-Ideas-For-Beautiful-Backyard-Landscape-32.jpg?fit=1024%2C819&amp;amp;amp;ssl=1&#34; alt=&#34;32 Awesome Small Pools Design Ideas For Beautiful Backyard Landscape&#34; title=&#34;32 Awesome Small Pools Design Ideas For Beautiful Backyard Landscape&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
32 Awesome Small Pools Design Ideas For Beautiful Backyard Landscape From magzhouse.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Endless pools ® has been solving that problem since 1988. For something small, however, you may be able to cut down on that cost. Other additional features will also determine the price of the pools such as the materials, finishes, special features (jacuzzi, lights, fountains, etc). From plunge pools and small fiberglass pools to tiny concrete pools and swimspas, there’s a material and.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Shower Tub Combo Ideas With DIY</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/shower-tub-combo-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/shower-tub-combo-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best Shower Tub Combo Ideas With DIY&lt;/strong&gt;, This is a great option if you have a tiny bathroom with limited space for a bathtub as well as a shower. Breaking up the tub and shower combo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/www.faburous.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/Mosaic-Tiles-bathroom.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Soaking tub shower combination ideas&#34; title=&#34;Soaking tub shower combination ideas&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Soaking tub shower combination ideas From faburous.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;/ 30 ways to style your shower and bathtub combo. View in gallery bathroom walk bathtub shower combo ideas 100 shower over bath ideas designs gorgeous tub. Enclosed tub and shower combo this is a great option if you want to maximize space in your bathroom. 30 ways to style your shower and bathtub combo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Brown Leather Bed Bedroom Ideas Simple Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/brown-leather-bed-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/brown-leather-bed-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Brown Leather Bed Bedroom Ideas Simple Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Primary bedroom featuring red walls and hardwood flooring. A sleek amber leather wingback headboard is a chic idea that adds coziness to the bedroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/b5/64/95/b56495ffefb69dde01ac0346e16e667d.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Tufted Leather bed gray wallsPB Bedroom decor&#34; title=&#34;Tufted Leather bed gray wallsPB Bedroom decor&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Tufted Leather bed gray wallsPB Bedroom decor From pinterest.com.au&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Primary bedroom featuring stylish flooring and red brick walls. Made with a solid wood frame upholstered in vinyl, tessie features tapered wood legs, plastic foot glides, ten sturdy wood slats with a centered supporting. A splash of brown leather for accents and dark brown wood finish for the furniture adds warmth and coziness. Brown is also a common color choice for modern décor, and paired with white, brown works well with scandinavian designs as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Rotating Shelf Bracket For Small Space</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/rotating-shelf-bracket/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/rotating-shelf-bracket/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Rotating Shelf Bracket For Small Space&lt;/strong&gt;, Plinth adjusting fitting with supporting bracket / load. These self adhesive 360 degree rotating rod brackets can be used more widely, great for walls and corners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/www-signaturehardware.com.imgeng.in/media/catalog/product/cache/1/image/680x/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/2/4/247840-victorian-cast-iron-hanging-plant-bracket-with-swivel-swing-arm-black-powder-coat-detail.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Victorian Cast Iron Hanging Plant Bracket with Swivel&#34; title=&#34;Victorian Cast Iron Hanging Plant Bracket with Swivel&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Victorian Cast Iron Hanging Plant Bracket with Swivel From signaturehardware.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to build vertical rotating shelves click image for larger versionname:wood rack 2.jpgviews:8970size:32.3 The steel pin wins the battle and the hole wears through. As well as from yes. Suitable for making tidy and organized bedroom, living room, dining room, kitchen, garden and office.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Small Tv For Small Room</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/small-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/small-tv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Small Tv For Small Room&lt;/strong&gt;, Not everyone has the space or budget for an enormous tv, but most of the tvs. 355 products filter sort by.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/bpc.h-cdn.co/assets/16/40/1600x800/landscape-1475527622-small-tvs.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;8 Best Small TVs Under 32 Inches in 2017 Small Flat Screen TVs&#34; title=&#34;8 Best Small TVs Under 32 Inches in 2017 Small Flat Screen TVs&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
8 Best Small TVs Under 32 Inches in 2017 Small Flat Screen TVs From bestproducts.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A hd experience in 720p provides crystal clear images. The best small tvs even though 55 inch and 65 inch have become the most popular tv sizes, smaller tvs are still important to many people. Not everyone has the space or budget for an enormous tv, but most of the tvs. It’s not exactly cheap at $500, but a reasonable option if you want full smart tv.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Stylish Nursery Ideas Simple Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/stylish-nursery-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/stylish-nursery-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Stylish Nursery Ideas Simple Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Simple &amp;amp; stylish scandinavian nursery decorating ideas. If it’s possible, put a comfy chair next to the bed to sit next to the baby and look after him or her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/projectnursery.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/BFAE7055-8C1F-40D7-8095-BC2D8F5C721C-e1549304546916.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Modern Neutral Nursery Project Nursery&#34; title=&#34;Modern Neutral Nursery Project Nursery&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Modern Neutral Nursery Project Nursery From projectnursery.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you want inspiration for planning a nursery renovation or are building a designer nursery from scratch, houzz has 18,370 images from the best designers, decorators, and architects in the country, including laurie demetrio interiors and livettes wallpaper. Stylish and functional nursery by oh eight oh nine. See more ideas about nursery, nursery inspiration, baby nursery. Welcoming a new human into the world is so much fun, but the waiting time can leave you antsy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free White Brick Walls With Low Cost</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/white-brick-walls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/white-brick-walls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free White Brick Walls With Low Cost&lt;/strong&gt;, Timber wall shelves combined with exposed bricks. This space shelters memory in an extraordinary frozen state of calm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i1.wp.com/waxcoastnj.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/cropped-white-brick-wall.jpg?ssl=1&#34; alt=&#34;croppedwhitebrickwall.jpg&#34; title=&#34;croppedwhitebrickwall.jpg&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
croppedwhitebrickwall.jpg From waxcoastnj.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Realistic light white brick wall background. White brick walls in the design of the kitchen add tons of character and texture. The white painted brick houses always look trendy. Adorn the wall with an aesthetically drawn pencil drawing or a beautiful painting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible Baby Pink Bedroom Ideas With New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/baby-pink-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/baby-pink-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incredible Baby Pink Bedroom Ideas With New Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Small pink nursery design [design: Shared blue and pink bedroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/projectnursery.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/10/turner-nursery-41.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Elegant and bold pink nursery Project Nursery&#34; title=&#34;Elegant and bold pink nursery Project Nursery&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Elegant and bold pink nursery Project Nursery From projectnursery.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to interior design, pink is a color that is popularly chosen for nurseries or children&#39;s bedrooms, but it is often shied away from in more common areas of the home. Muted decor is the typical choice for a baby’s room, although don’t limit your palette to pink and blue when thinking of boys and girls bedroom ideas! Pink nursery room for baby girl featuring a stylish crib, baby club chair and round pink rug. Use different textures and decor that will both soothe and stimulate your newborn, no matter their gender, and you can also experiment with nursery ideas such as wall stickers that will add.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible Bedroom Door Ideas With DIY</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/bedroom-door-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/bedroom-door-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incredible Bedroom Door Ideas With DIY&lt;/strong&gt;, You can have a contemporary bedroom that is clean and smooth and often pretty easy to clean. As a modern interior design evolves, a bedroom door is available in many styles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/homesfeed.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/Interior-door-home-made-from-wooden-with-small-blurred-parts.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Interior Door Designs for Homes HomesFeed&#34; title=&#34;Interior Door Designs for Homes HomesFeed&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Interior Door Designs for Homes HomesFeed From homesfeed.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most common type of doors, which use hinges for swinging action. Read the blog to know the top 20 master bedroom door design ideas and main bedroom door design. Replace your traditional, solid closet doors with a pair of shutters, then coat them in dark paint for a fresh, contemporary look. As a modern interior design evolves, a bedroom door is available in many styles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Bedroom Paint Color Ideas For Small Space</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/bedroom-paint-color-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/bedroom-paint-color-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Bedroom Paint Color Ideas For Small Space&lt;/strong&gt;, The best colors to paint your master bedroom for sleep. Bedrooms often use a dark paint colors like wild wisteria behind the headboard as an accent wall, and a lighter paint color like cosmic in the rest of the room to brighten up the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/theydesign.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/07/ideas-bedroom-interior-design-with-calming-paint-colors-of-grey-for-ideas-bedroom-interior-design-bedroom-decorations-images-what-color-to-paint-bedroom-with-regard-to-paint-ideas-for-bedroom-top-10-p.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Top 10 Paint Ideas for Bedroom 2017&#34; title=&#34;Top 10 Paint Ideas for Bedroom 2017&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Top 10 Paint Ideas for Bedroom 2017 From theydesign.net&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try a soft blue, green, purple, or grey. Dependable, versatile, warm, and subtle, these neutrals are some of the best paint colors for a bedroom. So, a color that is a little bit different from the other rooms in your house makes a huge difference to the ambiance. The most relaxing color for a bedroom is a blue gray color.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Paint Ideas For Childrens Bedroom Basic Idea</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/paint-ideas-for-childrens-bedroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/paint-ideas-for-childrens-bedroom/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Paint Ideas For Childrens Bedroom Basic Idea&lt;/strong&gt;, However, this should be done with care as a wrong choice can destroy the appeal of the entire room. Because it is for kids, you still have to put the features that can attract their attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/cdn.decoist.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/Kids-bedroom-paint-ideas-8.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Back to Kids Bedroom Paint Ideas 10 Ways to Redecorate&#34; title=&#34;Back to Kids Bedroom Paint Ideas 10 Ways to Redecorate&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Back to Kids Bedroom Paint Ideas 10 Ways to Redecorate From decoist.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s better to have less stimulating shades in the sleeping area, which makes pastel the perfect ally. If you are looking for more art projects, check out my collection of awesome painting ideas for kids. Keep everything organized and teach your children to keep their bedroom uncluttered so that your work will not be in vain. Add texture with thoughtful paint effects&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 Sample 3 Bedroom Apartment Ideas With New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/3-bedroom-apartment-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/3-bedroom-apartment-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Sample 3 Bedroom Apartment Ideas With New Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, In any small space, using mirrors is a decorating trick that works wonders. 3 bedroom house plans with 2 bathrooms or 2 1/2 bathrooms are the most common house plan configuration that people buy these days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/homedesignlover.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/08/9-829.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;20 Designs Ideas for 3D Apartment or OneStorey Three&#34; title=&#34;20 Designs Ideas for 3D Apartment or OneStorey Three&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
20 Designs Ideas for 3D Apartment or OneStorey Three From homedesignlover.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In any small space, using mirrors is a decorating trick that works wonders. Cheap 3 bedroom apartments near me for rent. Click the image for larger image size and more details. Browse 6,176 photos of 3 story apartment units.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 Sample Beach Condo Bedroom Decorating Ideas With DIY</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/beach-condo-bedroom-decorating-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/beach-condo-bedroom-decorating-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Sample Beach Condo Bedroom Decorating Ideas With DIY&lt;/strong&gt;, Modern and spacious beach front condominium. A starfish wreath blooming in the sun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/instaloverz.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/08/28-beach-style-master-bedroom.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;30 Beach Style Master Bedroom Decor Ideas&#34; title=&#34;30 Beach Style Master Bedroom Decor Ideas&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
30 Beach Style Master Bedroom Decor Ideas From instaloverz.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thrifty decorating ideas for a beach condo. We recommend a bench also, for laying out an open suitcase, and a peg rack on the wall near the door for hanging beach gear and extra towels. Drawings of different starfish, like the ones used by rmser rnhey, are perfect for summer. Doing this condo interior design does not need to be expensive, though.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 Sample Photo Collage Ideas For Bedroom Wall For Small Room</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/photo-collage-ideas-for-bedroom-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/photo-collage-ideas-for-bedroom-wall/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Sample Photo Collage Ideas For Bedroom Wall For Small Room&lt;/strong&gt;, Bedroom wall ideas for teens. Grid panel gallery wall pictures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/9f/09/90/9f0990cb8f682cc72518345829f2d5fc.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;pinterest annahallym in 2020 Picture wall bedroom&#34; title=&#34;pinterest annahallym in 2020 Picture wall bedroom&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
pinterest annahallym in 2020 Picture wall bedroom From pinterest.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Design your fridge with a gallery of pictures and fun memories. There are numerous design choices available, however the most popular is a great picture collage. Photo collage threetwentyeight postcard display diy wall art. When it’s not possible to hang something on your wall, you can still decorate it with this grid panel for your diy photo wall.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 Sample White Brick Design With New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/white-brick-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/white-brick-design/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Sample White Brick Design With New Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, White brick design sunday, september 24, 2017. While surfing the web for some new jewelry, i got really frustrated b/c i couldn&#39;t find any cool quote bracelets that were 1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/images.designtrends.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/29095646/White-Brick-Pattern.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;69&amp;#43; White Backgrounds, Wallpapers, Images, Pictures Design Trends&#34; title=&#34;69&amp;#43; White Backgrounds, Wallpapers, Images, Pictures Design Trends&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
69+ White Backgrounds, Wallpapers, Images, Pictures Design Trends From designtrends.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We love the white brick trend that has been circling the design world for some time now. Watch now and learn how you can achieve your white brick dream home! New structural supports are going in to. A white dining set and white pendant light are extra brilliant in front of a white brick wall.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Red And Grey Bedroom Designs Simple Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/red-and-grey-bedroom-designs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/red-and-grey-bedroom-designs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best Red And Grey Bedroom Designs Simple Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, See more ideas about bedroom red, bedroom, gray red bedroom. Thanks for visiting our gray primary bedrooms photo gallery where you can browse all kinds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/www.decorationlove.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/Red-and-Grey-Master-Bedroom.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;35 Stunning Gray Bedroom Design Ideas Decoration Love&#34; title=&#34;35 Stunning Gray Bedroom Design Ideas Decoration Love&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
35 Stunning Gray Bedroom Design Ideas Decoration Love From decorationlove.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discover bedroom ideas and design inspiration from a variety of bedrooms, including color, decor and theme options. Fashionable footstools bring the cowhide trend to the bedroom [design: It provides a rich contrast to the white bedding and walls. A crisp and classy design bedroom with clean black and cool shades of grey.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Bedroom Blackout Curtain Ideas With Low Cost</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/bedroom-blackout-curtain-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/bedroom-blackout-curtain-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Bedroom Blackout Curtain Ideas With Low Cost&lt;/strong&gt;, H.versailtex linen room darkening curtain panel; Driftaway thermal insulated 100 percent darkening blackout curtain liner 2 panels each liner size 50.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/i5.walmartimages.com/asr/2f7de8dd-7321-4209-9df1-b77393274059_1.beadd948757505310be301c111903ddd.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;HGMart Bedroom Curtains Blackout Drapery Panels&#34; title=&#34;HGMart Bedroom Curtains Blackout Drapery Panels&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
HGMart Bedroom Curtains Blackout Drapery Panels From walmart.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this case a blackout blind might be a better solution, to provide the same function as a blackout curtain. Make a bold statement by colour blocking in your bedroom and matching your curtain colour to your walls. Rosdorf park brockham solid blackout thermal grommet curtain panels; Pick yarn colors that complement your curtains, and this look can be achieved for under $5.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Modern Minimalist Bedroom Ideas With Low Cost</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/modern-minimalist-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/modern-minimalist-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Modern Minimalist Bedroom Ideas With Low Cost&lt;/strong&gt;, Best minimalist bedroom ideas minimalist bedroom ideas: Designers tow studios used elegant drapery and suspended bedside lights to create a moody, restful space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/cb/d0/91/cbd091752be62a60ed79bc4dd407a1a7.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;40 Modern Minimalist Bedroom Design Ideas&#34; title=&#34;40 Modern Minimalist Bedroom Design Ideas&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
40 Modern Minimalist Bedroom Design Ideas From pinterest.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having appliances such as the sound bar or television specially built into the custom designed carpentry is a great space saving idea, leaving more space for other decorative accessories. Best minimalist bedroom ideas minimalist bedroom ideas: Designers tow studios used elegant drapery and suspended bedside lights to create a moody restful space. Minimalism has long been a popular look for social areas of.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible 16 Year Old Bedroom Ideas For Small Room</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/16-year-old-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/16-year-old-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incredible 16 Year Old Bedroom Ideas For Small Room&lt;/strong&gt;, Diy picture frame with mosaic tiles. Sweet touches like a pink sheepskin pillow and frilly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/dd/c6/42/ddc642cb83ed33c7d6c7db58191b2d02.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Follow taiawoodard for more outfit insp. nail insp. skin&#34; title=&#34;Follow taiawoodard for more outfit insp. nail insp. skin&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Follow taiawoodard for more outfit insp. nail insp. skin From pinterest.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He wanted her to feel “understood” and validated as a girl entering into her teen years. This is one of those cartoon characters which is loved by every age group of people. Don&#39;t forget to save your favourite bedroom photos, ideas, colours, and layouts. Bunk beds for girls room.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible Grey And White Kitchen Ideas With Low Cost</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/grey-and-white-kitchen-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/grey-and-white-kitchen-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incredible Grey And White Kitchen Ideas With Low Cost&lt;/strong&gt;, Gray and white make for a sophisticated color. Combine dark grey units with bright white worktops, or light greys with smart black granite surfaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/ef/1b/84/ef1b8497e1dabacc8f2e5419bc763439.png&#34; alt=&#34;Neutral &amp;amp;amp; Noteworthy 13 Grey and White Kitchen Designs Kitchen&#34; title=&#34;Neutral &amp;amp;amp; Noteworthy 13 Grey and White Kitchen Designs Kitchen&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Neutral &amp;amp; Noteworthy 13 Grey and White Kitchen Designs Kitchen From pinterest.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gray and white make for a sophisticated color. Combine dark grey units with bright white worktops, or light greys with smart black granite surfaces. House for five featured on remodelaholic. A match made in heaven.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible House Design Colors Ideas Simple Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/house-design-colors-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/house-design-colors-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incredible House Design Colors Ideas Simple Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Browse color schemes and find decorating inspiration with our best color palette ideas. Elegant ceiling design ideas for your living room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/designermag.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/Ideas-for-Ethnic-Home-Decor.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Superb Ideas for Ethnic Home Decor Designer Mag&#34; title=&#34;Superb Ideas for Ethnic Home Decor Designer Mag&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Superb Ideas for Ethnic Home Decor Designer Mag From designermag.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Natural shades never go out of style. Browse color schemes to find color inspiration from interior design color palettes and choose the perfect color combinations for your designs. Small pooja room designs for indian homes. Top exterior color trends 2022:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible Swimming Pool Ideas For Small Backyards With DIY</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/swimming-pool-ideas-for-small-backyards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/swimming-pool-ideas-for-small-backyards/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incredible Swimming Pool Ideas For Small Backyards With DIY&lt;/strong&gt;, “most of the residential swimming pools we have built in the last five to 10 years are less than 600 square feet; The pool also features led colored lighting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/63/59/92/635992c8299634a8b745ede54d733bcc.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The best Small Inground Pool Ideas are those that offer you some more&#34; title=&#34;The best Small Inground Pool Ideas are those that offer you some more&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
The best Small Inground Pool Ideas are those that offer you some more From pinterest.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the right time to take action. It is a real refreshment in hot summer days with a swimming pool in your own backyard. Spruce up a traditional home with a free form pool in the backyard. A small pool can be circular, square, rectangular, or another shape that fits the space you have available.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List Of Colours To Go With Terracotta Tiles Simple Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/colours-to-go-with-terracotta-tiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/colours-to-go-with-terracotta-tiles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List Of Colours To Go With Terracotta Tiles Simple Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Terracotta comes in a range of colours from classic burnt orange tones, yellows, browns, and all the colours in between. The most popular colors that go with terracotta:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/ed/a1/3e/eda13e400e0f4bb6047cad0152ba0ca9.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The Most Beautiful Terracotta Tiles Our 24 Favorite Styles&#34; title=&#34;The Most Beautiful Terracotta Tiles Our 24 Favorite Styles&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
The Most Beautiful Terracotta Tiles Our 24 Favorite Styles From pinterest.com.mx&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A colour overlay showing how the scheme could look in situ. Shop faded terracotta from farrow and. Eagle design corner modernizing terracotta. New terracotta floor tiles color walls kezcreative.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List Of Cool Bedroom Ideas With Led Lights For Small Room</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/cool-bedroom-ideas-with-led-lights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/cool-bedroom-ideas-with-led-lights/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List Of Cool Bedroom Ideas With Led Lights For Small Room&lt;/strong&gt;, Make a statement with one or more of these ultra cool diy lighting ideas. Timeguard cool glow kids bedroom plug in night light with switch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/cdn.home-designing.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/neon-lights-LEDs-under-bed-blue-bedroom-ideas.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;30 Buoyant Blue Bedrooms That Add Tranquility and Calm to&#34; title=&#34;30 Buoyant Blue Bedrooms That Add Tranquility and Calm to&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
30 Buoyant Blue Bedrooms That Add Tranquility and Calm to From home-designing.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This can also help you figure out how much light you need, and what kind of fixtures make work best in the space. See more ideas about house design, led strip lighting, strip lighting. This type of fixture will provide up lighting and works especially well placed on either side of your bed above simple bedside tables. Timeguard cool glow kids bedroom plug in night light with switch.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List Of Cool Master Bedroom Ideas With New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/cool-master-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/cool-master-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List Of Cool Master Bedroom Ideas With New Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Spare no expense and do not compromise with your master bedroom ideas and designs. The master and mistress of the house deserve the best.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/2e/0f/b1/2e0fb18b5a49037c09eda40b4fbebbed.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Cool Master Bedroom Makeover Ideas 34 Master bedroom&#34; title=&#34;Cool Master Bedroom Makeover Ideas 34 Master bedroom&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Cool Master Bedroom Makeover Ideas 34 Master bedroom From pinterest.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hope to leave you with some ideas to revamp your own master bedroom, creating a personalized space that is both visually attractive an oasis of relaxation. To create a relaxing atmosphere for a master retreat, begin with a neutral color palette. You will get our expert consultation to get install a latest trending bedroom in. Below are 27 best pictures collection of master bedroom flooring ideas photo in high resolution.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List Of Help I Accidentally Built A Shelf Simple Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/help-i-accidentally-built-a-shelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/help-i-accidentally-built-a-shelf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List Of Help I Accidentally Built A Shelf Simple Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Tried online chat help and calling ikea customer service. I accidentally build a shelf!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/pics.onsizzle.com/help-i-accidentally-help-i-accidentally-meme-help-i-accidentally-66732883.png&#34; alt=&#34;🔥 25&amp;#43; Best Memes About Help I Accidentally Build a Shelf&#34; title=&#34;🔥 25&amp;#43; Best Memes About Help I Accidentally Build a Shelf&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
🔥 25+ Best Memes About Help I Accidentally Build a Shelf From onsizzle.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of them point to the idea that building flat box furniture like that from ikea can be addicting. Typing those words into a search engine can result in some hilarious articles and blog posts. I can tell if someone is mad at me because they send me a shelf for my birthday. 72% (464) help i accidentally shelf oh god.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List Of Magazine Bedroom Ideas Basic Idea</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/magazine-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/magazine-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List Of Magazine Bedroom Ideas Basic Idea&lt;/strong&gt;, Katie charlotte 2 of 55 Just remember to choose high contrast colors for text and backgrounds!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/img.sunset02.com/sites/default/files/image/2017/01/main/home-style-iconic-sunset-vanessa-de-vargas-bedroom-headboard-0913-m_0.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;11 Ideas for a More Colorful Bedroom Sunset Magazine&#34; title=&#34;11 Ideas for a More Colorful Bedroom Sunset Magazine&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
11 Ideas for a More Colorful Bedroom Sunset Magazine From sunset.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s why we&#39;ve put together this inspiring bedroom design guide. The 10 most popular house styles explained. Guest bedroom suite from hgtv smart home 2021 21 photos. Use furniture to create a comfortable and inviting bedroom environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>