<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bedroom on Bedroom Furniture Ideas</title>
    <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/tags/bedroom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bedroom on Bedroom Furniture Ideas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright 2022 [homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture](https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/tags/bedroom/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Free Interior Design Ideas Bedroom Vintage Simple Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/interior-design-ideas-bedroom-vintage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/interior-design-ideas-bedroom-vintage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Interior Design Ideas Bedroom Vintage Simple Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Choose rich red shades for a cozy feminine feel If you want to create a calm and relaxing atmosphere for your home or office,.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/interiorgod.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/20-Cool-Retro-Bedroom-Design-Ideas-To-Try.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;20 Cool Retro Bedroom Design Ideas To Try Interior God&#34; title=&#34;20 Cool Retro Bedroom Design Ideas To Try Interior God&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
20 Cool Retro Bedroom Design Ideas To Try Interior God From interiorgod.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether your style is minimal and modern or eclectic and bold, your bedroom should be a place that you can retreat to and recharge! Bedroom furniture in vintage style and french decorating ideas that include floral designs, soft pastels, light gray color tones, creamy. One needs to notice the soft colors, a fantastic array of fabrics used to pick up ideas for their own dream house and execute it in a way that masters both the look and the original concept together in the most. See more ideas about interior design, home, interior.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Ashley Furniture White Cabinet Basic Idea</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/ashley-furniture-white-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/ashley-furniture-white-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Ashley Furniture White Cabinet Basic Idea&lt;/strong&gt;, Or $34/mo suggested payments w/ 6 mos special financing learn how. Put your love of vintage style on display with this accent cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/s.yimg.com/aah/yhst-130038008324021/bush-furniture-salinas-farmhouse-bathroom-set-with-32w-vanity-medicine-cabinet-and-storage-in-linen-white-oak-sal027lw-14.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Bush Furniture Salinas Farmhouse Bathroom Set with 32W Vanity&#34; title=&#34;Bush Furniture Salinas Farmhouse Bathroom Set with 32W Vanity&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Bush Furniture Salinas Farmhouse Bathroom Set with 32W Vanity From afastores.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description with its distressed vintage paint finish, fluted details and french provincial mouldings, this exquisite cabinet is sure to grace your space in such a très chic way. Buy signature design by ashley mirimyn door accent cabinet, 4,. 1 cabinet with door and shelf; Filing cabinets are the perfect space for safely keeping all of your documents and files;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Moroccan Home Style With New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/moroccan-home-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/moroccan-home-style/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Moroccan Home Style With New Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Moroccan decor and design does not usually contain harsh lines and edges. Moroccan home decorating style evoke the wonder and sensuality through rich and lively colors and fabrics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/77/c9/b4/77c9b4789cc55408c92455fcf640b7ba.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Pin on Outdoor&#34; title=&#34;Pin on Outdoor&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Pin on Outdoor From pinterest.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elegant moroccan decorations look nice to define every home. The moroccan style is all about patterns and texture. Moroccan home decorating style evoke the wonder and sensuality through rich and lively colors and fabrics. Take trip morocco tips nail exotic via.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 Sample Modern House Blinds With New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/modern-house-blinds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/modern-house-blinds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Sample Modern House Blinds With New Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, What are the shipping options for modern blinds? Now homeowners have thousands of options to choose from to fit their desired aesthetic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/55/83/a2/5583a20035cd730a8e0c6c1486f215e0.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The Most Inspiring Midcentury Home Remodels Modern window coverings&#34; title=&#34;The Most Inspiring Midcentury Home Remodels Modern window coverings&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
The Most Inspiring Midcentury Home Remodels Modern window coverings From pinterest.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The latest trends for 2022. 25% off roof restoration + free gutter clean. In modern houses, apartments, and offices, minimalism dominates, as well as loft, japanese and scandinavian styles, allowing brevity and restraint to dominate almost uncompromisingly. There are plenty of styles of blinds that fit contemporary homes, such as colored wood blinds, leather blinds, and vertical panel tracks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List Of Ikea Shelves White Basic Idea</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/ikea-shelves-white/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/ikea-shelves-white/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List Of Ikea Shelves White Basic Idea&lt;/strong&gt;, Based on ikea lerberg shelf model made by rigel s., but improved with better details and textures. Genuine whirlpool wpw10276348 refrigerator glass shelf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/i.ebayimg.com/00/s/NzY4WDEwMjQ=/z/4RUAAOSwlndZOFTz/$_86.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;IKEA white Expedit 16 cube shelves storage RRP80 in&#34; title=&#34;IKEA white Expedit 16 cube shelves storage RRP80 in&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
IKEA white Expedit 16 cube shelves storage RRP80 in From gumtree.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ikea kallax shelving unit white 147×147 cm instruction manual. Select the nearest ikea store to check the stock availability of this product. Lack wall shelf, white, 431/4x101/4 (110x26 cm) this wall shelf has a clean design and has discreet and almost invisible mounting. They are available in a variety of different colours and sizes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Furniture Barn Tv Cabinet With Low Cost</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/furniture-barn-tv-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/furniture-barn-tv-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Furniture Barn Tv Cabinet With Low Cost&lt;/strong&gt;, Only you know what’s right for your home, but we’ve provided some pointers so you know what to look for in in a new tv table. The piece is finished in our natural tung oil rub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/furniturefromthebarn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/IMG_6315-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Weathered Gray X Style Barn Door Entertainment Furniture From&#34; title=&#34;Weathered Gray X Style Barn Door Entertainment Furniture From&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Weathered Gray X Style Barn Door Entertainment Furniture From From furniturefromthebarn.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Browse online or visit a local store today! Only you know what’s right for your home, but we’ve provided some pointers so you know what to look for in in a new tv table. Kosmo madarin tv unit in natural wenge melamine finish. Discover our range of contemporary, classic and modern tv units and entertainment units to complement your living room furniture.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Small Nyc Bedroom Ideas With Low Cost</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/small-nyc-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/small-nyc-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best Small Nyc Bedroom Ideas With Low Cost&lt;/strong&gt;, Today there is a better way than converting it into a reading nook, kitchen alcove or a space for shoe cabinet. Up your small bedroom’s cozy factor with warm, layered lighting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/1b/81/67/1b816767b8c1069b0092a1a422d15649.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;New York City Studio Bedrooms Small apartment decorating&#34; title=&#34;New York City Studio Bedrooms Small apartment decorating&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
New York City Studio Bedrooms Small apartment decorating From pinterest.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to decorating a small bedroom, first and foremost, it’s important to remember that the layout is everything. Decorative touches like the curtain wall for privacy will make a loft bed feel more like a bedroom than a top bunk. Folding screens, hanging wooden beads, or even several window panes not only act as dividers of spaces in a micro apartment but also give off the style desired in the space. Everyone wants to live in new york city, so most people have to pay top dollar for very small apartments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Bedroom Floor Mirror Ideas With New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/bedroom-floor-mirror-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/bedroom-floor-mirror-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Bedroom Floor Mirror Ideas With New Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, More mirrors for a bigger space “add a romantic touch by styling a gold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/i5.walmartimages.com/asr/c7383135-b3d5-4249-9a52-c8ed001a6ec4.ec25604d2a701f36846ccbea6974fe87.jpeg?odnWidth=1000&amp;amp;amp;odnHeight=1000&amp;amp;amp;odnBg=ffffff&#34; alt=&#34;Neutype Full Length Mirror Leaning Hanging 65&amp;amp;quot; x 22&amp;amp;quot; Large&#34; title=&#34;Neutype Full Length Mirror Leaning Hanging 65&amp;amp;quot; x 22&amp;amp;quot; Large&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Neutype Full Length Mirror Leaning Hanging 65&amp;quot; x 22&amp;quot; Large From walmart.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“add a romantic touch by styling a gold. Graceful distressed mirror over an entry table. This is especially ideal for bedrooms. Tall 7ft mirrors for more contemporary looks within contemporary floor standing mirrors view photo 5 of 15.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible Tinted Mirror With DIY</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/tinted-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/tinted-mirror/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incredible Tinted Mirror With DIY&lt;/strong&gt;, Because of the colored hue, manufactured into the glass, a tinted mirror might appear a little. The tinted mirrors are suitable for lobby decoration, wall cladding, guestroom, salon, mall, gym, fitness, hotel decoration, elevator interiors and other decorative purposes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/i.ebayimg.com/00/s/MTAyNFgxMDI0/z/R3EAAOSwhwpdLNEb/$_86.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;Rose copper coloured tinted mirror in Dundonald, Belfast Gumtree&#34; title=&#34;Rose copper coloured tinted mirror in Dundonald, Belfast Gumtree&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Rose copper coloured tinted mirror in Dundonald, Belfast Gumtree From gumtree.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turquoise green back paint for easy recognition. Tinted mirror is specialty coating with different colors, such as golden, brown, gray, blue, pink, black etc. Some of the tinted mirrors also have texture. Some tinted mirrors are true works of art, crafted to celebrate elements of design and creativity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List Of Small Master Bedroom Remodel Ideas For Small Space</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/small-master-bedroom-remodel-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/small-master-bedroom-remodel-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List Of Small Master Bedroom Remodel Ideas For Small Space&lt;/strong&gt;, My latest favorite is this cinnamon spiced vanilla candle that i got for mother’s day. This small master bedroom decorating ideas is better off painted with a dark blue night sky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/www.thespruce.com/thmb/Cx3JpCRDXPPYu5WH-yqo8gNRpwQ=/960x0/filters:no_upscale%28%29:max_bytes%28150000%29:strip_icc%28%29/small-master-25-586da5fd5f9b584db3797750.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Small Master Bedroom Design Ideas, Tips and Photos&#34; title=&#34;Small Master Bedroom Design Ideas, Tips and Photos&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Small Master Bedroom Design Ideas, Tips and Photos From thespruce.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Draw the eye upward, whether its by hanging items higher, getting a headboard that is a bit taller than usual, or painting the ceiling a lighter color than the rest. She added instant storage by adding two standalone closets flanking the bed. All you need to do is just picking the right furniture to make you feel comfy. Painting the walls with a new, improved colour.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List Of Spacious Bedroom Design Ideas Simple Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/spacious-bedroom-design-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/spacious-bedroom-design-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List Of Spacious Bedroom Design Ideas Simple Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Talk about a modern makeover! If you have not built your house yet and is about to build it, it is a good chance for you to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/s3.amazonaws.com/homestratosphere/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/shutterstock_48175261.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;43 Spacious Master Bedroom Designs with Luxury Bedroom&#34; title=&#34;43 Spacious Master Bedroom Designs with Luxury Bedroom&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
43 Spacious Master Bedroom Designs with Luxury Bedroom From homestratosphere.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clcik here to see more of our home interior design ideas. Also if you are unsure of where to start with the modern spacious guest bedroom design ideas nice or do not realize everything you&#39;re looking for, browsing our posts will be a fantastic place to get your begin. Building platforms and sliding the bed underneath, as an alternative to setting it on top, is a great way to save space in a small bedroom. The building is designed to include a kitchen, bathroom, living room, and optional bedroom on the first floor.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Teal Black And White Bedroom Ideas With Low Cost</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/teal-black-and-white-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/teal-black-and-white-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Teal Black And White Bedroom Ideas With Low Cost&lt;/strong&gt;, Teal bedroom ideas on turquoise aqua teal bedroom design interior. The colour pairs with white and black.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/9a/76/9d/9a769d14630d06f7e1fe1489bd5e3abf.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Teal, black, white, and gray bedroom I Decoupaged&#34; title=&#34;Teal, black, white, and gray bedroom I Decoupaged&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Teal, black, white, and gray bedroom I Decoupaged From pinterest.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It can also fit into different personalities and style preferences. Eclectic living room designs decorating ideas eclectic living room designs decorating ideas 10. Here are some of the best teal bedroom ideas you. No comments black white teal wall decor flower gray home and geometric shapes l stick removable wallpaper full size mural bedroom designs paint 17 ideas walls grey art 20 color combination trends in 2020 2021 rooms 25 abstract to help you add your large rose fl canvas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 Sample Light Blue And Gold Living Room With New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/light-blue-and-gold-living-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/light-blue-and-gold-living-room/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Sample Light Blue And Gold Living Room With New Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Sandy tones of light beige make this beachy living room exude comfort. A dark navy blue can elicit the cozy feeling of sitting under the night’s stars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/hgtvhome.sndimg.com/content/dam/images/hgtv/fullset/2011/2/8/0/HDSW1101_Living-Room-After-Look-2_s3x4.jpg.rend.hgtvcom.966.1288.suffix/1400961574972.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Living Room in Blue and Gold HGTV&#34; title=&#34;Living Room in Blue and Gold HGTV&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Living Room in Blue and Gold HGTV From photos.hgtv.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Palm tree titivates the room. It is amazing how the color blue can transform the feel of a room. A leather club chair and faux fur accents pile on the luxury while the colorful rug and velvet bean bag chair bring the whimsy. A cool hue living room feature navy blue living room with blue grey sofa accents and navy blue and grey cushions and grey rug.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List Of Cabinet Base Dimensions Simple Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/cabinet-base-dimensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/cabinet-base-dimensions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List Of Cabinet Base Dimensions Simple Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, The intended use of the base cabinet influences this decision. The plinth or toe kick height 2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/www.woodbridgebath.com/data/upload/20201013/content/5f855331c58c2_thumb_600x600.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ᐅ【Sydney 42&amp;amp;quot; inch Solid Wood Bathroom Vanity with White Solid Surface&#34; title=&#34;ᐅ【Sydney 42&amp;amp;quot; inch Solid Wood Bathroom Vanity with White Solid Surface&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
ᐅ【Sydney 42&amp;quot; inch Solid Wood Bathroom Vanity with White Solid Surface From woodbridgebath.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When cabinet height changes, lower opening height changes. The standard sizes for corner. With a blind base cabinet, you only have a small opening of typically 12, 15, or 18 inches to access the whole of the cabinet’s contents which can go as far back as 36 inches. The standard base cabinet width base is 34.5 inches tall with the exception of the countertop and 36 inches when the countertop is fitted.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Garden Swings For Small Space</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/garden-swings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/garden-swings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Garden Swings For Small Space&lt;/strong&gt;, We offer a complete and diversified line of products which will perfectly fit in your garden. According to the classification of archiproducts, the latter is called garden hanging chairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/www.backyardarea.com/images/products/CNOHPS51921-4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Outdoor 5Ft Slatted Porch Swing in Natural Acacia Wood with Hanging Chain&#34; title=&#34;Outdoor 5Ft Slatted Porch Swing in Natural Acacia Wood with Hanging Chain&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Outdoor 5Ft Slatted Porch Swing in Natural Acacia Wood with Hanging Chain From backyardarea.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Best garden swing chair for the porch: Plum colobus wooden garden swing set. This rustic garden swing embodies the raw beauty of branches and makes you feel like you are a part of nature itself! Tp round wood multi play centre.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free How To Decorate A Bachelor Bedroom Basic Idea</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/how-to-decorate-a-bachelor-bedroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/how-to-decorate-a-bachelor-bedroom/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free How To Decorate A Bachelor Bedroom Basic Idea&lt;/strong&gt;, These not only make you look like you have your life (and room) together but serve well in the winter when it gets a little chilly. Take a look at our bachelor bedroom ideas to get your creative juices flowing and build your design idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/www.homedoo.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/modern-contemporary-bedroom-design.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;6 best Ideas for the Bachelor Bedroom&#34; title=&#34;6 best Ideas for the Bachelor Bedroom&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
6 best Ideas for the Bachelor Bedroom From homedoo.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The unit separates the bedroom from the living room by lifting the mattress nearly three feet above the floor. 57 best men’s bedroom ideas. The bedroom proves a bachelor’s bedroom can look adorable. You can also forget about all the accessories and decorations such as plants and ornamental pieces.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List Of Arabian Themed Bedroom Ideas With DIY</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/arabian-themed-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/arabian-themed-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List Of Arabian Themed Bedroom Ideas With DIY&lt;/strong&gt;, Use these or download free. Arabian designs home plans | latest modern house ideas &amp;amp; collections | new stylish home collections of arabian designs | top 100+ modern villa plans &amp;amp; 3d elevation pictures online | best cheap exterior ideas &amp;amp; latest plans free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/2c/3b/ba/2c3bba07c4ba14708913d8ea9a19d521.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;62 Moroccan Themed Bedroom Design Ideas ROUNDECOR&#34; title=&#34;62 Moroccan Themed Bedroom Design Ideas ROUNDECOR&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
62 Moroccan Themed Bedroom Design Ideas ROUNDECOR From pinterest.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;( feinmann, inc.) potted greenery is essential to bring more natural touches to the interior. A calm and serene bedroom. See more ideas about bedroom, bedroom inspirations, house styles. Get a statement piece bed frame.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List Of Sophisticated Small Bedroom Ideas With DIY</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/sophisticated-small-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/sophisticated-small-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List Of Sophisticated Small Bedroom Ideas With DIY&lt;/strong&gt;, Display items that will fit your bedroom’s theme; Pairing white accents and wood tones with moody hues, including.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/www.mykidstime.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/06/modern-minimalist-bedroom-3147893_1280.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;8 Simple Small Bedroom Ideas to Make Your Room Look Great&#34; title=&#34;8 Simple Small Bedroom Ideas to Make Your Room Look Great&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
8 Simple Small Bedroom Ideas to Make Your Room Look Great From mykidstime.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since we heard so many times that dark color will make the room small, dark and feel depressive. Even in a sophisticated room with darker tones, you still need a variety of shades. With a tricky layout, this bohemian bedroom feels anything but crowded. Browse 169 sophisticated bathroom on houzz whether you want inspiration for planning sophisticated bathroom or are building designer sophisticated bathroom from scratch, houzz has 169 pictures from the best designers, decorators, and architects in the country, including relative design and see materials inc.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Cabinet Base Trim Ideas With New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/cabinet-base-trim-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/cabinet-base-trim-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Cabinet Base Trim Ideas With New Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Not sure if i should use 1/4 round, or try to make new toe kicks or what exactly i should do. See more ideas about baseboard trim, moldings and trim, baseboards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/www.heartwoodcarving.com/shop/images/trim16-2014-corner.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Carved Door Trim 18&#34; title=&#34;Carved Door Trim 18&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Carved Door Trim 18 From heartwoodcarving.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adding molding to a builder grade kitchen island from love remodeled. I am not to handy with. Learn how to trim cabinets properly in thi. The blocks along the back push this face out to about 1½ inches, making it suitable for use with deep, victorian style door.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Adventure Time Bedroom Ideas Simple Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/adventure-time-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/adventure-time-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Adventure Time Bedroom Ideas Simple Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Your two favorite movies (and how they’re similar and different). A future dictator invades the past.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/www.stylevore.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/Adventure-Time-Bed-Comforter-Set.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Jake the Dog, Bedding Set, Adventure Time on Stylevore&#34; title=&#34;Jake the Dog, Bedding Set, Adventure Time on Stylevore&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Jake the Dog, Bedding Set, Adventure Time on Stylevore From stylevore.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go check it out if you. A stack of old suitcases fit nice into. Sunnymead bed and breakfast (shimla), the bangala chettinad (tamil nadu), tangier (morocco), pura vida (costa rica), an bang beach homestay (vietnam) 13. Now trying to get them excited about anything can seem like more trouble than it’s worth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Brick Color House Paint With Trim Ideas For Small Room</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/brick-color-house-paint-with-trim-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/brick-color-house-paint-with-trim-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Brick Color House Paint With Trim Ideas For Small Room&lt;/strong&gt;, Try a matte black to look very modern, or a glossy. Black exterior trim can look stunning against red bricks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/thecolorconcierge.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/Brick-house-columns-perfect-768x534.png&#34; alt=&#34;Best exterior paint colors for red brick homes and how to use them&#34; title=&#34;Best exterior paint colors for red brick homes and how to use them&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Best exterior paint colors for red brick homes and how to use them From thecolorconcierge.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try a matte black to look very modern, or a glossy. Read on for exterior trim paint color ideas for brick houses. Black fences and red brick walls from. Trim colors for red brick houses.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List Of Clean Shower Head With DIY</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/clean-shower-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/clean-shower-head/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List Of Clean Shower Head With DIY&lt;/strong&gt;, Let the shower head soak for at least 30 minutes before removing the bag. Let the shower head soak in vinegar overnight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/www.lifesavvy.com/p/uploads/2019/05/c9e7742b.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;How to Clean Your Shower Head LifeSavvy&#34; title=&#34;How to Clean Your Shower Head LifeSavvy&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
How to Clean Your Shower Head LifeSavvy From lifesavvy.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3 clean the filter screen to clean. Thoroughly rinse it under the running water. The best ways to clean any shower. Rinse with a wet sponge or microfiber cloth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List Of Soccer Bedroom Ideas With Low Cost</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/soccer-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/soccer-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;List Of Soccer Bedroom Ideas With Low Cost&lt;/strong&gt;, Here in this video, we feature. Soccer ball themed girls bedding for bedroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/static1.squarespace.com/static/593dbd66cd0f68786f421739/598b34946f4ca31c8b3748fd/598b349b8419c293e1962f95/1504192597618/IMG_4542.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Soccer Themed Bedroom — Decor For Kids&#34; title=&#34;Soccer Themed Bedroom — Decor For Kids&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Soccer Themed Bedroom — Decor For Kids From decorforkids.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One common idea is to deck out a kid’s bedroom in a sports theme. See more ideas about bedroom themes, boys bedrooms, soccer bedroom. See more ideas about soccer bedroom, soccer room, soccer. Choose from lamps, trinket boxes, and picture frames that will get your kids psyched for gameday.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Home Office Ideas With New Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/home-office-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/home-office-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Home Office Ideas With New Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, Photo by the beauty dojo. Scandinavian home office with green wall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/houzhero.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/30-Incredible-Home-Office-Inspiration-Ideas-For-Men-5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;30 Incredible Home Office Inspiration Ideas For Men Page 5 of 30&#34; title=&#34;30 Incredible Home Office Inspiration Ideas For Men Page 5 of 30&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
30 Incredible Home Office Inspiration Ideas For Men Page 5 of 30 From houzhero.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you want inspiration for planning a modern home office renovation or are building a designer home office from scratch, houzz has 31,950 images from the best designers, decorators, and architects in the country, including john kraemer &amp;amp; sons and danze &amp;amp; davis architects, inc. Inspiration for a traditional home office in london with white walls, medium hardwood flooring, a freestanding desk and brown floors. A double drawing room, family room, snug, study and hall on the first and ground levels, and a. Save your interactions for last.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 Sample Grey And Mint Green Bedroom Ideas Basic Idea</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/grey-and-mint-green-bedroom-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/grey-and-mint-green-bedroom-ideas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Sample Grey And Mint Green Bedroom Ideas Basic Idea&lt;/strong&gt;, Also you can just put some piece of furniture in mint or peach color that will lighten up your space. Whether you want inspiration for planning a green bedroom renovation or are building a designer bedroom from scratch, houzz has 14,405 images from the best designers, decorators, and architects in the country, including the iconic space and shanly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/16/6d/f6/166df6329280edee6fb54dac74b16e78.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Green and White Bedroom Get the Look Sarah Richardson&#34; title=&#34;Green and White Bedroom Get the Look Sarah Richardson&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Green and White Bedroom Get the Look Sarah Richardson From pinterest.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look through grey and mint. Bedroom color scheme ideas will help you to add harmonious shades to your home which give variety and feelings of calm. From the minty green wall tiles to the freestanding sinks, matte finishes, terrazzo vanity, and hairpin legs, it&#39;s pretty hard not to. Whether you want inspiration for planning a green bedroom renovation or are building a designer bedroom from scratch, houzz has 14,405 images from the best designers, decorators, and architects in the country, including the iconic space and shanly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Bedroom Furniture Ideas Minecraft For Small Room</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/bedroom-furniture-ideas-minecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/bedroom-furniture-ideas-minecraft/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best Bedroom Furniture Ideas Minecraft For Small Room&lt;/strong&gt;, And the bed is designed to become the main focal point with its colorful hues. Storage, shelving and furniture ideas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/14/e6/a6/14e6a6087863b1e60cb25da57f6fd4d0.png&#34; alt=&#34;Awesome furniture idea! Credit typfacemc Minecraft&#34; title=&#34;Awesome furniture idea! Credit typfacemc Minecraft&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Awesome furniture idea! Credit typfacemc Minecraft From pinterest.jp&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Add a minecraft feel to it. An idea for a more interesting home is to have themed chests with only certain things. One great furniture idea for a minecraft bedroom is a desk. Think cubed when it comes to storage ideas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best How To Decorate Bachelor Pad Simple Ideas</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/how-to-decorate-bachelor-pad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/how-to-decorate-bachelor-pad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best How To Decorate Bachelor Pad Simple Ideas&lt;/strong&gt;, The choice of faucets &amp;amp; wc’s is rectangular in shape. Tips for decorating your space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/coodecors.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/33-%e2%88%9a-Bachelor-Pad-Mens-Bedroom-Ideas-Manly-Interior-Design-6.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;33 √ Bachelor Pad Mens Bedroom Ideas Manly Interior Design 6 coodecors&#34; title=&#34;33 √ Bachelor Pad Mens Bedroom Ideas Manly Interior Design 6 coodecors&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
33 √ Bachelor Pad Mens Bedroom Ideas Manly Interior Design 6 coodecors From coodecors.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The choice of faucets &amp;amp; wc’s is rectangular in shape. View in gallery bachelor pad ideas. Even a tiny room needs a place for you to unwind. Chic small dining room ideas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible Cool Teen Rooms For Small Space</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/cool-teen-rooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/cool-teen-rooms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incredible Cool Teen Rooms For Small Space&lt;/strong&gt;, Play ball sport teenage boy room theme. A printed upholstered headboard and fun throw pillows will bring in a sense of youthfulness while modern sconces add polish, like in this room by amber interiors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/house-interior.net/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/Teen-room-15-1024x1024.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Teen room 2020 Newest ideas for teen room design ( 32&amp;#43; Photo &amp;#43; Videos)&#34; title=&#34;Teen room 2020 Newest ideas for teen room design ( 32&amp;#43; Photo &amp;#43; Videos)&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Teen room 2020 Newest ideas for teen room design ( 32+ Photo + Videos) From house-interior.net&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’ve been stuck on how to get the most out of your teenager’s bedroom, these designs will give you some very stylish things to think about. A printed upholstered headboard and fun throw pillows will bring in a sense of youthfulness while modern sconces add polish, like in this room by amber interiors. Our first cute bedroom ideas are proof that teen girls room decor is becoming more sophisticated. A printed upholstered headboard and fun throw pillows will bring in a sense of youthfulness while modern sconces add polish, like in this room by amber interiors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible How To Make A Wall Art For Small Space</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/how-to-make-a-wall-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/how-to-make-a-wall-art/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incredible How To Make A Wall Art For Small Space&lt;/strong&gt;, How to create a gallery wall in eight easy steps choose your winning pieces. These distinguished pieces add class to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/topdreamer.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Tree-branch-wall-lighting.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Branches Wall Decor Ideas That Will Steal The Show&#34; title=&#34;Branches Wall Decor Ideas That Will Steal The Show&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
Branches Wall Decor Ideas That Will Steal The Show From topdreamer.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose the following settings and hit “print”: Use the template to plot out where each frame will go on. Grab some fun scrapbook paper, punch out some circles and sprinkle them onto a canvas. Trace the frame you&#39;re using on a piece of paper to make a template, then mark the top center point of the template.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Corner Shelf Unit Ikea Basic Idea</title>
      <link>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/corner-shelf-unit-ikea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homext.github.io/bedroom-furniture/corner-shelf-unit-ikea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Corner Shelf Unit Ikea Basic Idea&lt;/strong&gt;, Best shag rugs ikea style &amp;amp; comfort. Curvy details and shelves of glass and steel are ready to accommodate your folded towels and beauty products to create a personal and charming look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; src=&#34;https://homext.github.io/img/placeholder.svg&#34; data-src=&#34;https://i2.wp.com/images.kaiyo.com/12554/ikea/storage/bookcases-shelving/used-ikea-ronnskar-corner-shelf-unit.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;37 OFF IKEA IKEA RONNSKAR Corner Shelf Unit / Storage&#34; title=&#34;37 OFF IKEA IKEA RONNSKAR Corner Shelf Unit / Storage&#34; onerror=&#34;this.onerror=null;this.src=&#39;https:\/\/homext.github.io\/img\/placeholder.svg&#39;;&#34; class=&#34;center&#34; /&gt;
37 OFF IKEA IKEA RONNSKAR Corner Shelf Unit / Storage From kaiyo.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It fits in the smallest of bathrooms, but there’s plenty of space on the shelves for all your toiletries from shampoo bottles to soap and small items. Best ikea bathrooms ideas remodel. 0% installment 30 days return. Carefully measure the seating area.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>